Witness the Most Evil, Disturbing Movie of All Time. You wont just be scared. You will be SCARRED. What you
are about to see are Satan's Proudest Moments. You wont believe your Eyes . . . or Stomach!
Slaughtered Vomit Dolls is a horror, drama film directed by Lucifer Valentine.
The gruesome tapestry of psychological manifestations of a nineteen year old bulimic runaway
stripper-turned prostitute as she descends into a hellish pit of satanic nightmares and hallucinations.
Angela Aberdeen, played by Ameara Lavey.
Princess Pam, played by Pam McCartney.
Slaughtered Vomit Dolls is a 2006 Canadian surrealist exploitation psychological horror film written and directed by Shawn Fedorchuk (as Lucifer Valentine), who
coined the subgenre of extreme horror movies known as "vomit gore.”  The film had a simultaneous DVD and limited theatrical release on February 14, 2006.
The film follows a very loose plot structure, consisting of assorted random scenes mostly
revolving around Angela Aberdeen, a bulimic stripper-turned-prostitute.
Slaughtered Vomit Dolls is a part of the Vomit Gore Trilogy and was followed by two
sequels: ReGOREgitated Sacrifice (2008) and Slow Torture Puke Chamber (2010).
A fourth film – titled Vomit Gore 4: Black Mass of the
Nazi Sex Wizard – was released in 2015.
Most recently, in May 2020, the anthology film The Angela Chapters was released.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.